hello welcome to 2024 and we hope things
are off to a good start for you we now
have 14 ongoing projects at The
Institute ranging from textbook and
skill development groups to various
research projects feel free to read
about the projects and their
documentation and that page which is
projects. active inference
coming in the next 7 Days the event name
where the meeting online is being held
and the calendar event if you want to
add it to your own time zone and also
all the projects that are active right
now at the Institute this is broken out
into the educational edu active
organizational unit and Reiner or
Research Unit within each unit there are
projects that are hosted at The
Institute these are open source open
science type initiatives that everyone's
welcome to join and contribute to to and
also projects that have been proposed
from the ecosystem in education and in
application secondly the measurement
form for reporting your updates on
projects whether they are hosted at The
Institute or not is now open these
updates may be shared by the officers to
the monthly newsletter Board of director
scientific Advisory Board Etc ideally
getting your exciting projects the
visibility and resources that will
further your work so if you have any
updates from your work in the active
inference ecosystem be it edits to an
Institute project or epistemic foraging
far field we would very much like to
hear from you about
this here's the project measurement form
all the fields are optional and they ask
things about what you've done what you
measured how it contributed to active
inference what you could use to take
your project
further otherwise thank you contact us
at blanket active inference Institute
with any questions thank you and onwards
officers